(MlCHAEL GRUNTlNG)
MlCHAEL: Okay.
DWlGHT: Breathe. (GROANS)
Work your core!
(GROANS) Come on.
How many is that?
Not counting the last one, 25.
Count the last one.
Okay, 25 and one girl pushup.
Oh, new record !
Okay. Oh !
What did you do today?
l made a sale.
(CHUCKLlNG) Oh, yeah, sitting on your big fat butt.
All right, that is the number to beat.
What do we get if we do them?
My respect.
Okay, l'll make it a little more interesting.
Anyone who does more than 25 pushups. . .
And one girl pushup.
. . .gets to go home.
(DWlGHT AND MlCHAEL EXCLAlMlNG)
(DWlGHT AND MlCHAEL LAUGHlNG)
l say "dance," they say "how high?"
ANDY: Three, four. . .
Here we go. No, no, no, butt too high.
Disqualified ! (EXCLAlMS)
What do we got? Creed, disqualified.
Oh, come on !
JlM: Nineteen.
(GROANS)
l had a really hard workout this morning.
(GROANlNG)
Oh, wow! That is adorable!
PHYLLlS: Ten. DWlGHT: Yeah !
l'm betting one more.
Eleven.
PHYLLlS: Wow! Good.
ALL: Stanley! Stanley! Stanley! Stanley! Stanley!
All right. All right.
ALL: Stanley! Stanley! Stanley!
Essentially what we have here is one of those stories
where a mother lifts a car to save her baby.
Well, it's not exactly fair.
He's got all this weight that's helping him go down.
ANDY: Twenty-five! PHYLLlS: Come on !
One more! One more, Stanley! Yeah, come on ! You can do it.
Come on, Stanley! Let's do it. Come on.
DWlGHT: Go!
JlM: Yes!
(ALL CHEERlNG)
Yes! ANDY: Yeah !
(ALL WHOOPlNG)
OSCAR: Are you okay? MlCHAEL: Very nicely done.
OSCAR: Are you okay, Stanley?
Excuse me.
(PHYLLlS CHUCKLlNG)
(EXHALES)
DWlGHT: Wow.
All right, Papa Bear.
(HORN HONKS)
Hey!
Matt, right?
Hey, Oscar. You're here early.
(SCOFFS) No. l always come in at 7:00.
No you don't.
Well. . .
Hey, are you doing anything later tonight?
l don't know. l'm free.
lf you hear of anything going on, let me know.
Yeah.
Yeah, we talked this morning,
and we talked at Christmas,
so a little momentum there.
Couple hours to kill before work.
Hey, what's up? Hey.
Nice office.
Thanks. lt's cool.
(SNlFFLES)
So. . .
You know what we haven't done in a while?
Happy hour.
Upstairs, the warehouse, everybody just going out for a drink.
Has that ever happened? Ever?
Didn't we? l think we did.
Want me to invite Matt?
Yeah, the whole gang. Matt included.
Look, just be straight with me, man.
You can be gay with Matt, just be straight with me.
So, happy hour. Happy hour.
Just invite everybody.
My pleasure.
OSCAR: All right.
So, what do you think? PHYLLlS: Hmm.
l saw a new drink on TV l'd like to try.
l'll ask Bob.
Yeah. l love going to bars with Bob.
l tend to wear something low-cut,
get men to flirt with me, and Bob beats them up.
What?
A bunch of us are talking about happy hour.
l would love, love, love to go.
Only problem is,
Pam's at home with the baby and l think she wants a night in.
Oh, baloney. Good one.
Ring her up.
Absolutely. l'll do that right now.
l gotta tell you, this baby is amazing.
She gets me out of everything.
And l love her. l also love her very much.
So, some of the coworkers
were thinking of going out tonight, but l told them. . .
PAM: Yes! Yes, I wouId Iove to!
(EXCLAlMS) Knew it!
It's been so long since I've been with aduIts.
I'm so excited to see everybody.
Creed, Ryan. Oh, my God, StanIey!
StanIey's gonna be there. Yes! Oh, my God...
l did not see this coming.
Erin, l need you to fax this and get me a confirmation, pronto.
Are you going later?
Sure, if you are. Yes.
Talk to me that way again and l'll cut your face off.
Whoa!
We recently struck up a romantic relationship, and. . .
But we're kind of keeping it quiet for now,
'cause it's still kind of a new thing, it's a little delicate,
and we just don't want all the drama. Exactly.
Yeah, 'cause when everyone knows, it. . . (KNOCK ON WlNDOW)
(LAUGHlNG)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's actually pretty funny, but in general, you know. . .
(KEVlN LAUGHlNG)
Quiet.
Hey, boss man. MlCHAEL: Yes.
A bunch of us are going to get some drinks. You in?
Ladies and gentlemen, it is quitting time.
l'm sorry, l meant later.
Okay. Yes. For happy hour?
Sure. No, l got that.
Trying to get a head count.
l am in !
All right.
Yes. lt's a deal.
lt's a deal.
Hey, l invited my friend Julie. Okay.
l want her to meet Michael.
Why?
They're both single. l have a sense they might. . .
You've been gone for a long time.
lt is not that. . . Kevin !
Yeah !
How are you?
Oh, l missed you so much. Oh !
Yeah.
(lMlTATlNG BABY CRYlNG)
Well, when a new mom hears a baby cry,
her you-know-whats fill up with you know what,
and then her shirt gets, you know. . .
(GlGGLES) That would be funny.
Oh, wow. l cannot believe this is happening. This is everything l dreamed.
Oh, my God !
Hey!
(LAUGHS) Easy.
lt's not a birthday, it's not a goodbye party.
Hey, Pam and l are gonna go play pool
with one of her friends, and we need a fourth.
Sucks to be you.
Would you like to be our fourth?
That would be sublime.
All right.
So, the guy shows me the deck he's built,
and l'm like, "l'll call this a deck if it'll make you happy,
"but this is just a porch without a roof."
(ALL CHUCKLlNG)
DARRYL: lt was ridiculous, man.
lt was, like, you could maybe get two chairs on the thing.
Two lawn chairs.
Hey, Michael. Yes?
This is my friend Julie.
MlCHAEL: Hello. How are you? Hi.
What is a nice girl like you hanging out with these bums for?
There you go.
Julie laughs at everything.
So you work with Pam and Jim?
Oh, no, no. Pam and Jim work for me,
and if they win, they are fired.
(CHUCKLlNG) l should hope not.
(CHUCKLES) No. No. Not really. Not really. But they better not win.
Hey. PAM: Hey, lsabel, you made it.
Oh, my goodness! Of course.
You want to play pool?
l'm gonna do a lap, see if l know anyone. Okay.
And then they said the most ridiculous thing about Anderson Cooper,
which l do not have the decency to repeat,
but trust me when l tell you that it. . .
Hold that thought.
Well, well, well.
(CHUCKLES)
lf it isn't lsabel. Mmm-hmm.
What's a girl like you doing in a place like this?
A girl like me is why a guy like you comes to a place like this.
Ooh. l love repartee.
Do you?
Usually means there's a battle scene coming.
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
So what do you do?
l am an ESL teacher.
Really? Yeah.
See, l didn't think you could teach that.
l thought that was something you were born with.
What am l thinking right now?
Are you thinking that l said ESP?
Yes. l feel like an idiot. Awesome.
l was a little nervous when Pam told me he was her boss,
but he doesn't act like a boss at all.
lf l had a boss like that, we'd never get anything done.
So what do you think?
About what?
About Julie?
She seems nice.
Yeah? Yeah.
So you like her? Uh, yeah, sure.
So Pam was right.
About what?
About you two hitting it off.
Well, apparently Michael Scott is on a date,
and that. . . That, my friend, changes everything.
My brother, good head, bad heart. Good head, bad heart.
OSCAR: l know.
PAM: Yeah, you told me about him. JULlE: Yeah.
PAM: Oh, boy! JULlE: He's all right.
Hey, Michael, where have you been?
Hey, you're supposed to hit the white ball first, buddy.
Hey! Nice one.
Can l talk to you for a second? Mmm-hmm.
Everything okay? Why are you wearing a hat now?
Guys, come on. l'm on a date.
Let me do my thing.
Hi, l'm Date Mike. Nice to meet me.
How do you like your eggs in the morning?
Do you want to just make a run for it?
Maybe.
(lMlTATlNG BABY CRYlNG)
Mommy!
What is happening?
(MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Whoa!
What is cracking? One second.
Guys, we're focusing. We can't talk.
What's this game? One second.
Yeah. How do you play?
Guys, guys, guys, please. Okay.
All right, it's all yours. Only three tickets.
lf we save them up, we can get more than a sticker this time.
Stop telling me how to spend my tickets.
l know, but you wanted. . .
Wow! Can you imagine what people would say
if they saw us dancing together?
Oh, l know.
They'd be like, "What's up with those two?"
"Hey, guys, get a bedroom already."
"Did we miss the wedding?"
l got it. l'll do this and you play the racing game
and then we'll switch.
Yes. Okay. Yeah, that's smart.
No drama. Okay.
Oh, air hockey, basketball.
We could play that.
Oh, Whac-A-Mole.
Any brothers or sisters?
Three brothers. Really?
Mmm-hmm. Two are in the Marines, one's a cop.
Vegetarian?
No. l love meat.
(CHUCKLlNG)
What's your blood type?
O negative. Universal donor.
Universal donor! Mmm-hmm.
(BLEEP)
Angela versus lsabel. Height, advantage lsabel.
Birthing hips, advantage lsabel.
Remaining childbearing years, advantage lsabel.
Legal obligation, advantage Angela.
Hey, guys, guys, guys. Excusez-moi. Hey.
Watch this. Ready?
What are you doing?
l'm tying a knot in the stem with my tongue.
Michael, you don't have to do this.
(GAGGlNG)
Wow. That was close.
l would say l kind of have an unfair advantage,
because I watch reality dating shows like a hawk.
And I Iearn. I absorb information
from the strategies of the winners and the Iosers.
Actually, l probably learn more from the losers.
Hey, you two having fun?
Did you tell them?
No.
This is exactly what l don't want.
The drama.
l don't want the drama!
Oh.
You are amazing at this. How did you get so good?
Whacking moles. Hit him on the head. Whack!
Whack! Whack! Say it with me.
Whack! Extend the fingers more.
Whack! Good.
This looks like a hoot.
Hey, monkey, how you doing? Whack.
Listen, can l talk to you for a second?
Okay.
(SlGHS) You know, l've been thinking, we had a good run,
we really did, but you don't need to worry
about this whole contract thing anymore.
lt's no worry.
lt's just that we both. . . We want different things.
You know, l want a big family.
l could see enjoying that.
No, no, no, no, no. l want a big family.
Tall, thick. A big, physically big family.
Listen, you go have fun.
You're off the hook.
But we signed the contract.
lt's dissolved. Don't worry. You're free.
Okay? Okay. We'll see you later.
But we both. . . And you didn't do. . .
(GUlTAR PLAYlNG)
Wow! Maybe we should tell her he's not normally like this.
Maybe it should come from a man.
Maybe it should come from a note.
With flowers. Tomorrow.
Hello. Hello.
Hi. Hi.
You want to pay 400 bucks to re-felt this table?
Yeah ! Why don't you send the bill
to 23 l Don't Care Lane, Scranton, Pennsylvania?
Hey, Michael, why don't you just get down?
Hey, she can tell l'm on a date, right?
Right? We're just having fun.
Ted, we having fun?
Really? You told on me. That's lame.
We got a problem? Yes. Homelessness.
(LAUGHlNG)
What? All right, go.
Where?
Get out. Now.
Okay. All right, okay. Whoa!
(EXHALES)
l'm just kidding around. l'm sorry.
Okay, why don't we just finish the game?
Michael, it's your shot.
She can't talk to us that way.
You guys are stripes, l think.
You let somebody talk to you like that,
where does it stop?
lt stopped.
Well, l am starting it again !
Do you guys want some food?
The wings are really good here.
(POP MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Hey!
You embarrassed my friends in front of me, and l am gonna need you
to go back over to the table and apologize.
Then l am sorry that l didn't kick you out.
l'm here with my employees. l am here on a date.
Hello.
Well, l'm the manager here, sir.
Well, it just so happens that l'm a manager, too,
and the way l manage people is that l touch their hearts and souls
with humor, with love and maybe a dash of razzle-dazzle,
and l don't see that from you.
ls that how you do it?
Yes, it is. l'm writing a book about it.
Really? How much have you written?
l've written all of it.
ln my head.
lf you're really interested, it is called Somehow I Manage,
and there's going to be a picture of me on the cover shrugging
with my sleeves rolled up.
Have you read Lee lacocca's? lt's classic.
Read it? l own it.
But no, l have not read it.
Dude, tonight.
You're not gonna want to put it down. lt's gonna make you want
to go out and buy a Chrysler tomorrow.
l own a Chrysler.
Shut up.
No, you shut up.
What's your drink?
Grenadine.
What?
We just have to throw everyone off the scent a little, so follow my lead.
Hi. Hi.
l don't normally do this, but. . . Do what?
Go, go. Just sit down next to a beautiful woman
and start talking to myself to confuse other people.
Hey, big boy. Do you like it when l do that?
What are you doing?
What we said to do.
We didn't say we were gonna, like, start groping strangers.
l was flirting with a man.
Get in here.
Where did you learn to talk like that?
ERlN: The movies. l don't know.
ANDY: What movie? BIack Snake Moan?
l manage a paper company. Dunder Mifflin-Sabre.
Do you have a card?
l did. l actually put it in your bowl.
Stanley Hudson?
No. No.
Whoa! A lot of Stanley Hudsons in here.
No, it's Michael Scott.
Michael Scott?
He is l.
You just won yourself a lunch.
Oh. Hey, guys!
l think l'm gonna go.
Really?
l'm sorry. He's not usually like that.
What's he usually like?
He's more just. . .
Like. . . You can go. Yeah.
All right.
Bye. See you.
Nice girl. Yeah.
Hey! Julie, having fun?
(CLEARS THROAT) So, when are you coming in for that free lunch?
You're gonna want to come in on a day that l'm working.
Maybe l can hear more about that book, too.
Hey, man. You put together a pretty fun night for everybody.
l saw you talking to Hide. Did you hear that dude's life story?
lt's amazing, right?
l couldn't understand a word he said.
Let me tell you something, Oscar, all right?
Matt's an okay dude, but he's a dummy.
You guys got nothing in common.
Maybe you're right. l should count myself lucky.
Hey, what's up?
There he is! Hey!
Anyone up for some hoops? Yeah. Hoops!
Let's do it. OSCAR: Hoop it. Yeah.
This is not what l want my relationship to look like.
Hi, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Andrew Bernard and I've been on two dates with Erin Hannon
and they went well, and there will probably be more.
Thank you.
You know, it got to the point
where keeping it a secret was just too much drama.
And l hate drama, so. . . There you go.
You love drama.
l know, l do, right?
(BOTH LAUGHlNG)
l'm a total drama queen.
This move? He can't get you.
l think that he could counter that move.
The Scranton Strangler is a professional strangler.
Oh, please. l wish he'd come after me. l would be like. . .
Dwight Schrute!
Dwight Kurt Schrute. Shut up, what?
You are hereby served with this summons
to appear in Lackawanna County court. . .
No, no, no. . . .for breach of contract
against Angela Noelle Martin.
What are you talking about? What are you. . .
Dwight recently entered into a contract with me, establishing intent
to conceive and raise a child with me. Angela.
Did he not tell you that? What?
You're really putting me in an awkward position here.
Do you plan on raising a child with me,
or do you plan on breaking this contract?
Angela! Not here!
Dwight.
Whack.
(RAZZlNG)
You will see me in small claims court!
You are an impressive specimen.
Thank you.
(CRYlNG)
And l spilled my drink and they wouldn't give me a refill.
Oh, my gosh. Okay, yeah, we have to get home.
Okay. Yes!
Halperts, wait up! What a great night!
Got to hang out with my peeps.
Sort of did okay with a new young lady.
Actually you didn't. Not at all.
l think l did, but l can't take all the credit.
Some of the credit is due, in fact, to my good friend Date Mike.
Nice to meet me.
Tell me your story, Hide.
(SPEAKlNG)